[
  {"question": "ğŸ’", "response": "ğŸ’"},
  {"question": "ğŸš«", "response": "ğŸš«"},
  {"question": "ğŸ¥³", "response": "ğŸ¥³"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‘", "response": "ğŸ‘"},
  {"question": "ğŸ˜‹", "response": "ğŸ˜‹"},
  {"question": "ğŸ¤–", "response": "ğŸ¤–"},
  {"question": "ğŸ®", "response": "ğŸ®"},
  {"question": "ğŸ˜¬", "response": "ğŸ˜¬"},
  {"question": "ğŸŒš", "response": "ğŸŒš"},
  {"question": "ğŸŒ›", "response": "ğŸŒ›"},
  {"question": "ğŸ˜", "response": "ğŸ˜"},
  {"question": "ğŸ¤¡", "response": "ğŸ¤¡"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‘¿", "response": "ğŸ‘¿"},
  {"question": "ğŸ˜ˆ", "response": "ğŸ˜ˆ"},
  {"question": "ğŸ¥¶", "response": "ğŸ¥¶"},
  {"question": "ğŸ¥µ", "response": "ğŸ¥µ"},
  {"question": "ğŸ™Š", "response": "ğŸ™Š"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‘½", "response": "ğŸ‘½"},
  {"question": "ğŸ˜»", "response": "ğŸ˜»"},
  {"question": "ğŸ’¤", "response": "ğŸ’¤"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‘»", "response": "ğŸ‘»"},
  {"question": "ğŸ”¥", "response": "ğŸ”¥"},
  {"question": "ğŸ’¦", "response": "ğŸ’¦"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‰", "response": "ğŸ‰"},
  {"question": "ğŸ’Œ", "response": "ğŸ’Œ"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‘Œ", "response": "ğŸ‘Œ"},
  {"question": "ğŸ’ª", "response": "ğŸ’ª"},
  {"question": "ğŸ§”", "response": "ğŸ§”"},
  {"question": "ğŸªµ", "response": "ğŸªµ"},
  {"question": "ğŸ¼", "response": "ğŸ¼"},
  {"question": "ğŸ¦Š", "response": "ğŸ¦Š"},
  {"question": "ğŸ", "response": "ğŸ"},
  {"question": "ğŸš€", "response": "ğŸš€"},
  {"question": "ğŸ—½", "response": "ğŸ—½"},
  {"question": "âœˆï¸", "response": "âœˆï¸"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‚", "response": "ğŸ‚"},
  {"question": "ğŸ", "response": "ğŸ"},
  {"question": "ğŸ„", "response": "ğŸ„"},
  {"question": "ğŸ†", "response": "ğŸ†"},
  {"question": "ğŸˆ", "response": "ğŸˆ"},
  {"question": "âš½", "response": "âš½"},
  {"question": "ğŸ¯", "response": "ğŸ¯"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‘¾", "response": "ğŸ‘¾"},
  {"question": "ğŸ©", "response": "ğŸ©"},
  {"question": "ğŸ¨", "response": "ğŸ¨"},
  {"question": "ğŸ˜±", "response": "ğŸ˜±"},
  {"question": "ğŸ¤—", "response": "ğŸ¤—"},
  {"question": "ğŸŒ»", "response": "ğŸŒ»"},
  {"question": "ğŸŒŠ", "response": "ğŸŒŠ"},
  {"question": "ğŸŒˆ", "response": "ğŸŒˆ"},
  {"question": "â˜˜ï¸", "response": "â˜˜ï¸"},
  {"question": "â„ï¸", "response": "â„ï¸"}
]